https://paint-test-equipment.co.uk/cookie-policy/

sales@paint-test-equipment.com +44 (0)1260 275614
Search for:
GBPUSDEUR WOOCS v.2.2.8.1
GBPUSDEUR WOOCS v.2.2.8.1
Toggle navigation
MENUMENUHomeAboutProductsCoating ThicknessCoating Thickness MeterUSB Download CableFerrous ProbesNon-Ferrous ProbesCalibration FoilsZero DiskWet Film ThicknessNEW Wet Film GaugeWet Film Gauges PlasticInspection KitPaint Inspection KitPorosityHoliday DetectorBroad Holiday BrushCircular Holiday BrushRolling Holiday SpringRolling Spring ConnectorExtension RodBand BrushHigh Voltage HandleEarth CablePinhole DetectorGlossGloss MeterElectrostatic Gun MeterAdhesionDigital Adhesion TesterAdhesion TesterConcave Adhesion DollyConvex Adhesion DollyFlat Adhesion DollyTurbo Fuse AdhesiveDolly PlugsCross Hatch CutterSurface RoughnessTestex Replica TapeReplica Tape GaugeReplica Tape Burnishing ToolsSurface Roughness ComparatorSurface CleanlinessBresle Patch TestBresle PatchesBresle Deionised WaterBresle SyringesBresle BeakersBresle Cond Meter SensorBresle Calibration SolutionBresle Conditioning SolutionDust Tape TestDust Test TapeDust Test ComparatorPotassium Ferricyanide PapersISO Rust Grade BookDewpoint MeterCalibrationContact
Basket× Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the Service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which Cookies are installed may also require the User’s consent.Where the installation of Cookies is based on consent, such consent can be freely withdrawn at any time following the instructions provided in this document.Technical Cookies and Cookies serving aggregated statistical purposesActivity strictly necessary for the functioning of the ServiceThis Website uses Cookies to save the User’s session and to carry out other activities that are strictly necessary for the operation of this Website, for example in relation to the distribution of traffic.Activity regarding the saving of preferences, optimisation, and statisticsThis Website uses Cookies to save browsing preferences and to optimize the User’s browsing experience. Among these Cookies are, for example, those used for the setting of language and currency preferences or for the management of first party statistics employed directly by the Owner of the site.Other types of Cookies or third parties that install CookiesIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Some of the services listed below collect statistics in an anonymized and aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties.If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information.AdvertisingThis type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioural retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behaviour, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.In addition to any opt-out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioural retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behaviour, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.In addition to any opt-out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Google AdSense (Google Inc.)If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behaviour concerning ads, products and services offered.Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout.AnalyticsThe services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behaviour.Google Ads conversion tracking (Google Inc.)If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Google Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google Ads advertising network with actions performed on this Website.Google Analytics (Google Inc.)Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out. Privacy Shield participant.Infrastructure monitoringThis type of service allows this Website to monitor the use and behaviour of its components so its performance, operation, maintenance and troubleshooting can be improved.Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and mode of implementation of these services, whose function is to filter the activities of this Website.StatusCake (TrafficCake Limited)StatusCake is a monitoring service provided by TrafficCake Limited.Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.Place of processing: United Kingdom – Privacy Policy.Remarketing and behavioral targetingThis type of service allows this Website and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Website by the User.This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioural targeting activity.In addition to any opt-out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Google Ads Remarketing (Google LLC)Google Ads Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioural targeting service provided by Google LLC that connects the activity of this Website with the Google Ads advertising network and the DoubleClick Cookie.Users can opt out of Google’s use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out. Privacy Shield participant.How to provide or withdraw consent to the installation of CookiesIn addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies.Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website.Users can, for example, find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses: Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Microsoft Internet Explorer.With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party’s privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the EDAA (EU), the Network Advertising Initiative (US) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (US), DAAC (Canada), DDAI (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.Owner and Data ControllerPaint Test Equipment 3–4 The Courtyard Greenfield Farm Estate Congleton, Cheshire CW12 4TR EnglandOwner contact email: painttestoffice@aol.comSince the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Website cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by this Website.Definitions and legal referencesPersonal Data (or Data)Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Usage DataInformation collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.UserThe individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.Data SubjectThe natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.Data Controller (or Owner)The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.This Website (or this Application)The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.ServiceThe service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.European Union (or EU)Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.CookiesSmall sets of data stored in the User’s device.Legal informationLegal informationThis privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.Download Catalogue 2020Download Price List 2020ProductsCoating ThicknessWet Film ThicknessInspection KitPorosityAdhesionSurface CleanlinessSurface RoughnessGlossContact Details sales@paint-test-equipment.com +44 (0)1260 275614Address Head Office, Paint Test Equipment
3–4 The Courtyard, Greenfield Farm Estate
Congleton, Cheshire, CW12 4TR, EnglandWant to receive regular updates on the latest products, news from us?
Leave this field empty if you're human: By entering your email address above, you're consenting for Paint Test Equipment to send our newsletters, offers and promotions directly to your inbox. In compliance with data protection laws we will not share this information with any other thrid party or organisations. If you'd like to opt out of our mailing list at any time, simply click unsubscribe in the footer of the emails you receive from us.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
